A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Series A FA310
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence - Legal Residence, 1933-1937 (Box 38, Folder 293)
  Change from 54th Street to Pocantico Hills in 1935.
- Correspondence - Newcomen Society Dinner and Speech, 1947-1949 (Box 38, Folder 294)
  Study of John D. Rockefeller prepared by Allan Nevins and W. Trevor Holliday for dinner, March 4, 1948. Talk was later printed and widely distributed.
- Correspondence - Occupancy of Kykuit, 1935-1937 (Box 38, Folder 295)
- Correspondence - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1933-1942 (Box 38, Folder 296)
  Republication of book in 1933 by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (JDR Jr.). Sale and distribution. Reprinted in 1937, JDR Jr. underwriting costs. Requests for permission to quote book. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Ivy Lee.
- Correspondence - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1943-1961 (Box 38, Folder 297)
- Correspondence - Taxes - Boulware, A. L., 1922-1923 (Box 38, Folder 298)
- Correspondence - Stock Market Statement, October-November 1929 (Box 39, Folder 299)
  John D. Rockefeller's confidence in values; reaction to statement.
- Correspondence - Testimonials, 1929, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 300)
  From Spencerian School and City of Bayonne, New Jersey.
- Correspondence - Unauthorized Use of Name, 1920-1921 (Box 39, Folder 301)
  For oil schemes, savings program.
- Death - Announcements/Certificate, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 302)
- Death - Condolences, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 303)
- Death - Condolences - Lists and Form Letters (Box 39, Folder 304)
  Lists of people who received acknowledgement of condolences.
- Death - Condolences/Replies (A-B), 1937 (Box 39, Folder 305)
  Acknowledged by John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Death - Condolences/Replies (C-D), 1937 (Box 39, Folder 306)
- Death - Condolences/Replies (E-H), 1937 (Box 39, Folder 307)
- Death - Condolences/Replies (I-L), 1937 (Box 39, Folder 308)
- Death - Condolences/Replies (M-N), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 309)
- Death - Condolences/Replies (O-R), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 310)
- Death - Condolences/Replies (S-T), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 311)
- Death - Condolences/Replies (U-Z), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 312)
- Death - Condolences/Replies (A-P), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 313)
  Copies.
- Death - Condolences/Replies (R-Z), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 314)
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Churches and Religious Organizations, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 315)
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Churches and Religious Organizations, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 316)
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Colleges and Schools, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 317)
  Memorial services at Peking Union Medical College and University of Chicago.
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Colleges and Schools, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 318)
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Colleges and Schools, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 319)
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Foreign Governments, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 320)
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Foreign Governments, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 321)
- Death - Condolences - Not Acknowledged, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 322)
- Death - Condolences/Replies - Organizations, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 323)
- Death - Condolences to John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 324)
- Death - Condolences to Nelson A. Rockefeller (A-L), 1937 (Box 41, Folder 325)
- Death - Condolences to Nelson A. Rockefeller (M-Z), 1937 (Box 42, Folder 326)
- Death - Funeral - Lakeview Cemetery, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 327)
  Flowers, placing of stone, protection of grave.
- Death - Funeral Services at Pocantico Hills, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 328)
  Preparations; attendance; Dr. Foskick's prayer, printed copies.
- Death - Letters to Newspapers (Box 42, Folder 329)
  Appreciation for way in which press handled news of John D. Rockefeller's death and burial. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Death - Letters to Trainmen (Box 42, Folder 330)
  Letters of appreciation for services rendered. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Death - Memorial at National Cathedral, 1937-1942 (Box 42, Folder 331)
  Douglas Freeman suggested tablet dedicated to John D. Rockefeller in Cathedral in Washington, D.C.; financed by 25 southern colleges and universities. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. acknowledged gifts by schools. Correspondents include Douglas S. Freeman, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Death - News Clippings (Box 42, Folder 332)
  Unorganized.
- Death - News Clippings (Box 42, Folder 333)
- Death - News Clippings (Box 42, Folder 334)
- Death - Resolutions from Organizations, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 335)
  From oil companies, American Petroleum Institute, towns, Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), Baptist Convention, Chamber of Commerce of New York, Rockefeller Institute. Proposed memorials.
- Death - Resolutions from Organizations, 1937-1938 (Box 43, Folder 336)
- Death - Resolutions from Organizations, 1939-1940, 1954-1956 (Box 43, Folder 337)
- Death - Resolutions - Cleveland, Cleveland Heights, East Cleveland, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 338)
  Resolutions.
- Death - Resolutions - New Jersey Memorial Highway, 1937-1940 (Box 43, Folder 339)
  Highway memorial established and maintained road; some trees from Lakewood used in landscaping.
- Driving Club, 1899-1901 (Box 43, Folder 340)
- Erie Street Baptist Church - Minutes, 1851-1884 (Box 43, Folder 341)
- Estate, 1937-1941 (Box 43, Folder 342)
- Estate - Last Will and Testament (Box 43, Folder 343)
- Euclid Avenue Baptist Church, 1884 (Box 43, Folder 0343A)
  Cross-reference only.
  See Box 60, Folder 477.
- Finances - Correspondence, 1896-1908 (Box 44, Folder 344)
  Investment policies; 1907 Panic; Rockefeller office reaction. Charging off of old debts. Critical analysis of the Gould system. Studies of stock and bond holdings. Stock market and call loan market activities. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, George Rogers, E. V. Cary, Frederick T. Gates.
- Finances - Correspondence, 1909-1914 (Box 44, Folder 345)
- Finances - Correspondence, 1915-1924 (Box 44, Folder 346)
  John D. Rockefeller's stock and bond investments; money loaned on call; changes in investments. Income investment; percent of Standard companies owned by John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in 1923; list of notes and loans charged off on John D. Rockefeller's books. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Bertram Cutler, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Finances - Correspondence, 1926-1933 (Box 44, Folder 347)
  Interest rates allowed John D. Rockefeller on money deposited with John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Inter-family loans; old debts; handling of dividend payments. Daily cash reports from office to John D. Rockefeller. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Bertram Cutler, Philip Keebler.
- Finances - Correspondence, 1934-1937 (Box 44, Folder 348)
- Finances - Data and Codes, 1931-1937 (Box 44, Folder 349)
- Finances - Income Lists, 1905-1918 (Box 44, Folder 350)
  Monthly income statements; interest on bonds; stock dividends; other income. Correspondents include E. V. Cary, J. Jenkins, John D. Rockefeller.
- Finances - Securities Donated, 1913-1916 (Box 45, Folder 351)
  Tabulation of John D. Rockefeller Ledger and Inventory value of securities as of March 1, 1913; value of securities donated 1913-1916.
- Finance Committee - Minutes, 1908-1909 (Box 45, Folder 352)
  Committee of Frederick T. Gates, H. E. Cooper, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.; discussed financial affairs and investments. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frederick T. Gates, H. E. Cooper.
- Folsom College - Practice Books (Box 45, Folder 0352A)
  See Box 60, Folders 478-481.
- Genealogy - Rockefeller, 1934-1941 (Box 45, Folder 353)
- Genealogy - Avery Family - Correspondence, 1895-1900 (Box 45, Folder 354)
  John D. Rockefeller (JDR) contribution to Avery Memorial in Groton, Connecticut and to memorial window in Groton church; underwrote genealogy of Avery family prepared by Elroy Avery. Request for information and aid from members of Avery family; incidental information on members of family. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Elroy M. Avery, Starr J. Murphy.
- Genealogy - Avery Family - Correspondence, 1901-1910 (Box 45, Folder 355)
- Genealogy - Avery Family - Correspondence, 1911-1961 (Box 45, Folder 356)
- Genealogy - Davison Family - Correspondence, 1919-1947 (Box 45, Folder 357)
  Requests for aid and information from Davisons; one manuscript chart of Davison genealogy. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
- Genealogy - Rockefeller Family - Correspondence, 1895-1906 (Box 45, Folder 358)
  John D. Rockefeller contributed to Rockefeller memorial in western New Jersey cemetery; underwrote Oscar Rockefeller's genealogy of family. Search for actual burial place of Johann Peter Rockefeller; research in Germany. Requests for aid and information from members of family. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Oscar Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy.
- Genealogy - Rockefeller Family - Correspondence, 1907-1960 (Box 46, Folder 359)
- Genealogy - Spelman Family - Correspondence, 1896-1902 (Box 46, Folder 360)
  Laura Spelman Rockefeller helped finance study of Spelman genealogy; material collected in United States and Great Britain; folio prepared on English line. 1910, complete genealogy published. Requests for aid and information from members of Spelman family. Correspondents include Laura Spelman Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy.
- Genealogy - Spelman Family - Correspondence, 1903-1909 (Box 46, Folder 361)
- Genealogy - Spelman Family - Correspondence, 1910-1961 (Box 46, Folder 362)
- Gifts - Endowment, 1929-1947 (Box 46, Folder 363)
- Gifts - Family - Birthday Instructions, 1905-1935 (Box 46, Folder 364)
  Payment authorizations for $100 gifts to grandchildren on their birthdays. $1000 gifts to children on John D. Rockefeller's birthday. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller.
- Gifts - Family, 1915-1922 (Box 46, Folder 365)
  Worksheets showing gifts made in this period.
- Gifts - Family (Statistics), 1936 (Box 46, Folder 366)
- Gifts - Individuals, 1877-1936 (Box 46, Folder 367)
- Gifts - Individuals, 1877-1936; 2 copies. (Box 47, Folder 368)
- Gifts - Individuals and Institutions, 1907-1937 (Box 47, Folder 369)
- Gifts - Report - Armour Correspondence, 1935-1955 (Box 47, Folder 370)
  Compilation of John D. Rockefeller's giving by A. W. Armour of the General Education Board. Does not include gifts to individuals. Use of record; copy of study. Correspondents include A. W. Armour.
- Gifts - Report - Armour, 1936-1937 (Box 47, Folder 371)
- Gifts - Report - Armour, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 372)
- Gifts - Report - Armour (Incomplete), 1937 (Box 47, Folder 373)
- Gifts - Preliminary Report of Gifts Valued at $5,000, 1937 (Box 47, Folder 374)
- Gifts - Schedule of Gifts Valued at $5,000 or More (Box 047A, Folder 0374A)
- Gifts - Schedule of Gifts Valued at $5,000 or More - Duplicate Copies (Box 047A, Folder 0374B)
- Gifts - Miscellaneous Data, 1921-1961 (Box 047A, Folder 0374C)
  Various compilations of John D. Rockefeller's giving; used by Ivy Lee.
- Public Benefactions, 1855-1935 - Report by A. W. Armour (Box 047A, Folder 374)
- Golf Record, 1913 (Box 047A, Folder 375)
- Household Expenses, 1911-1913 (Box 047A, Folder 376)
  Statements on housekeeping expenses.
- Journal, 1918-1924 (Box 047A, Folder 377)
- Gifts - Schedule of Gifts Valued at $5,000 or More (Box 047A, Folder 0374A)
- Gifts - Schedule of Gifts Valued at $5,000 or More - Duplicate Copies (Box 047A, Folder 0374B)
- Gifts - Miscellaneous Data, 1921-1961 (Box 047A, Folder 0374C)
- Public Benefactions, 1855-1935 - Report by A. W. Armour (Box 047A, Folder 374)
- Golf Record, 1913 (Box 047A, Folder 375)
- Household Expenses, 1911-1913 (Box 047A, Folder 376)
- Journal, 1918-1924 (Box 047A, Folder 377)
- Oil Business - Article - "A Lampful of Oil", January 1886 (Box 48, Folder 378)
  Printed in Harper's New Monthly Magazine.
- Oil Business - South Improvement Company - Statement by W. G. Warden, 1872 (Box 48, Folder 379)
- Oil Business - Standard Oil Company - Donations, 1882-1883 (Box 48, Folder 0379A)
  See Box 60, Folder 482.
- Oil Business - Standard Oil Company - Executive Committee Minutes, January-November 1880 (Box 48, Folder 380)
- Oil Business - Standard Oil Company - Executive Committee Minutes, November 1880-July 1882 (Box 48, Folder 381)
- Oil Business - Standard Oil Company - Payroll Book, 1880 (Box 48, Folder 382)
- Oil Business - Standard Oil Company - Stock Certificates (Box 48, Folder 383)
- Oil Business - Standard Oil Company of Pittsburgh - Stock Certificates (Box 48, Folder 0383A)
- Owego Academy - Catalogue, 1853 (Box 48, Folder 384)
- Pledge Lists, 1894-1903 (Box 48, Folder 385)
- Pledge Lists, 1904-1906 (Box 48, Folder 386)
- Pledge Lists, 1907-1909 (Box 49, Folder 387)
- Pledge Lists, 1910-1912 (Box 49, Folder 388)
- Pledge Lists, 1913-1916 (Box 49, Folder 389)
- Pledge Lists, 1917-1919 (Box 49, Folder 390)
- Pledge Lists, 1920-1922 (Box 49, Folder 391)
- Pledge Lists, 1923-1925 (Box 49, Folder 392)
- Pledge Lists, 1926-1928 (Box 49, Folder 393)
- Pledge Lists, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 394)
- Pledge Lists - Organizations, 1913-1915 (Box 50, Folder 395)
- Power of Attorney, 1915-1927 (Box 50, Folder 396)
- Properties - Forest Hill - General, 1886, 1917-1923, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 397)
  Clippings, 1982.
- Properties - Forest Hill - Automobiles - Roads, 1916-1923 (Box 50, Folder 398)
- Properties - Golf House - General, 1908, 1918-1920 (Box 50, Folder 399)
- Properties - Golf House - General, 1921 (Box 50, Folder 400)
- Properties - Golf House - General, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 401)
- Properties - Golf House - General, 1923 (Box 50, Folder 402)
- Properties - Golf House - Automobiles, 1919-1923 (Box 51, Folder 403)
- Properties - Golf House - Cows, 1919-1923 (Box 51, Folder 404)
- Properties - Golf House - Employees
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Open for scholarly research with prior archival review.
  - 1919-1920 (Box 51, Folder 405)
  - 1921 (Box 51, Folder 406)
  - 1922 (Box 51, Folder 407)
  - 1923 (Box 51, Folder 408)
- Properties - Golf House - Heating, 1919-1923 (Box 51, Folder 409)
- Properties - Golf House - Land, 1918-1923 (Box 51, Folder 410)
  See also Box 67, Folder 11.
- Properties - Golf House - Sheep, 1917-1923 (Box 51, Folder 411)
- Properties - Golf House - Water, 1918-1923 (Box 52, Folder 412)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, 1910-1911 (Box 52, Folder 413)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, 1912 (Box 52, Folder 414)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, 1913-1918 (Box 52, Folder 415)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, 1919 (Box 52, Folder 416)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, January-June 1920 (Box 52, Folder 417)
  See also Box 67, Folders 2 and 3.
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, July-December 1920 (Box 52, Folder 418)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, January-June 1921 (Box 52, Folder 419)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, July-December 1921 (Box 53, Folder 420)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, January-May 1922 (Box 53, Folder 421)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, June-October 1922 (Box 53, Folder 422)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, November-December 1922 (Box 53, Folder 423)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, January-May 1923 (Box 53, Folder 424)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, June-October 1923 (Box 53, Folder 425)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, November-December 1923 (Box 53, Folder 426)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, January-September 1924 (Box 53, Folder 427)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, October-December 1924 (Box 54, Folder 428)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 429)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - General, 1926-1934 (Box 54, Folder 430)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Automobiles, 1911, 1913, 1919-1923 (Box 54, Folder 431)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Automobiles, 1924-1926, 1929-1930 (Box 54, Folder 432)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Cows, 1919-1924 (Box 54, Folder 433)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Cows, 1925-1930 (Box 54, Folder 434)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Employees
  - 1910-1918 (Box 54, Folder 435)
    Including garden and construction expenses.
  - 1919 (Box 54, Folder 436)
  - 1920 (Box 55, Folder 437)
  - 1921 (Box 55, Folder 438)
  - 1922-February 1923 (Box 55, Folder 439)
  - March 1923-1924 (Box 55, Folder 440)
  - 1925-1932 (Box 55, Folder 441)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Heating, 1910, 1914, 1919-1921 (Box 55, Folder 442)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Heating, 1922-1923 (Box 55, Folder 443)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Heating, 1924-1926, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 444)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Land, 1910-1911, 1915-1927 (Box 56, Folder 445)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Articles, c. 1907, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 0445A)
  Copies of articles about stables (pre-1907) and Eastview purchase (1929).
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Poultry, 1919-1928 (Box 56, Folder 446)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Roads, 1910-1920 (Box 56, Folder 447)
  See also Box 67, Folder 4.
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Roads, 1921-1923 (Box 56, Folder 448)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Roads, 1924-1932 (Box 56, Folder 449)
  See also Box 67, Folder 5.
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Sheep, 1918-1926 (Box 56, Folder 450)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Water, 1911-1923 (Box 56, Folder 451)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Water, 1924-1930 (Box 56, Folder 452)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Works of Art, 1910-1917, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 453)
- Publicity - Correspondence, 1903-1937 (Box 57, Folder 454)
- Publicity - Correspondence, 1940-1954 (Box 57, Folder 455)
- Publicity - Correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box 57, Folder 456)
- Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1908-1909 (Box 57, Folder 457)
  As serialized in The World's Work. Folder is empty.
  See also Box 38, Folders 296-297 for correspondence.
- Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1908-1909 (Box 57, Folder 458)
- Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1908-1909 (Box 57, Folder 459)
- Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1908-1909 (Box 57, Folder 460)
- Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1908-1909 (Box 57, Folder 461)
- The Altoviti Aphrodite, by Welles Bosworth, 1920; Copy 1 of 3 (Box 057A, Folder 1)
  Privately printed.
- The Altoviti Aphrodite, by Welles Bosworth, 1920; Copy 2 of 3 (Box 057A, Folder 2)
- The Altoviti Aphrodite, by Welles Bosworth, 1920; Copy 3 of 3 (Box 057A, Folder 3)
- Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1908-1909 (Box 58, Folder 462)
- Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, 1908-1909 (Box 58, Folder 463)
- Rockefeller Family Association - Correspondence, 1910-1932 (Box 58, Folder 464)
  Purchase of genealogies. Attempt to interest John D. Rockefeller (JDR) in financing relatives' education. JDR membership in Rockefeller Family Association; research in Europe; JDR Jr. became life member in 1938. JDR Jr. underwrote part of cost of Volume IV of genealogy. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson.
- Rockefeller Family Association - Correspondence, 1933-1937 (Box 58, Folder 465)
- Rockefeller Family Association - Correspondence, 1938-1951 (Box 58, Folder 466)
- Rockefeller Family Association - Correspondence, 1952-1961 (Box 58, Folder 467)
- Rockefeller Family Association - Simon Rockefeller Homestead, 1938-1939 (Box 58, Folder 468)
  John D. Rockefeller, Jr. limited amount of funds he would contribute for purchase.
- Rockefeller Family Association - Burial Ground, Flemington, New Jersey, 1905-1954 (Box 58, Folder 469)
  Discovery of small private graveyard on former lands of Johann Peter Rockefeller; offers to sell it to John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Blackmail attempts; protection of graves. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Starr J. Murphy, Charles O. Heydt, Willard S. Richardson.
- Rockefeller Companies - Cancelled Checks of Rockefeller & Company; Rockefeller, Andrews & Flagler, 1866-1868 (Box 58, Folder 470)
- Stationery - Cards (Box 59, Folder 471)
  Calling cards, business cards, and declination cards to be sent to those requesting money.
- Stationery - Verse Cards (Box 59, Folder 472)
  Printed copies of the following poems:"I was early taught""I do it unto thee...""Somebody did a golden deed""The best memory system""But as we met"
- Stationery - Ormond Beach Letterhead (Box 59, Folder 473)
- Miscellaneous - Address Book/Gift Listing, 1918-1937 (Box 59, Folder 474)
- Miscellaneous, 1907 (Box 59, Folder 475)
  See also Box 60, Folder 483.
- California Trip - Vouchers and Bills, 1884 (Box 60, Folder 476)
- Euclid Avenue Baptist Church, 1884 (Box 60, Folder 477)
- Folsom College - Practice Books, 1854-1855 (Box 60, Folder 478)
- Folsom College - Practice Books - Day Book, 1854-1855 (Box 60, Folder 479)
- Folsom College - Practice Books - Journal, 1854-1855 (Box 60, Folder 480)
- Folsom College - Practice Books - Ledger, 1854-1855 (Box 60, Folder 481)
- Oil Business - Standard Oil Company (Cleveland, Ohio and New York) - Donations, 1882-1883 (Box 60, Folder 482)
- Miscellaneous - Song Dedication, 1909 (Box 60, Folder 483)
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr. - Property Appraisal, c. 1931 (Box 60, Folder 484)
- Properties - Pocantico Hills - Appraisal of Estate, 1924 (Box 61, Folder 485)
- Rockefeller Family - Judgement Taken Before William Rockefeller, June 27, 1818, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 486)
  Document purchased by Nelson A. Rockefeller.
- Rockefeller Family - Storekeeper's Ledger, Oak Hill, New York, 1867-1876 (Box 62, Folder 487)
- Rockefeller Family - Storekeeper's Ledger, 1846-1869 (Box 62, Folder 488)
- Rockefeller Family - General, 1937-1958 (Box 63, Folder 489)
  Requests for photographs, etc.
- Rockefeller Family - Birth Certificates, 1936-1953 (Box 63, Folder 490)
  Restricted material.
  Copies of birth certificates of some members of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s family; incomplete.
- Rockefeller Family - Letters of Appreciation, 1949-1960 (Box 63, Folder 491)
  Letters to family expressing appreciation for the good it was doing; some answered by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Some routinely acknowledged.
- Rockefeller Family - Photographs, 1940-1960 (Box 63, Folder 492)
  Correspondence regarding the purchase of the Koshiba negatives. Policies about use of family photographs.
- John D. Rockefeller, Jr. - Pledge Lists, 1918-1920 (Box 63, Folder 493)
- Estate Work Papers - Cash Reports (Box 063A, Folder 1)
  Ledger pages, bank statements, balance at bank at close of business, April 22, 1939, with reports back to July 26, 1937, journal entries.
- Estate of John D. Rockefeller - Current Papers, 1938-1942 (Box 063A, Folder 2)
  Trial balances; list of employees, their years of service, and allowances after John D. Rockefeller's death.
- Estate of John D. Rockefeller - Correspondence and Reports, 1930-1949 (Box 063A, Folder 3)
- Data Relative to the Death of John D. Rockefeller on May 23, 1937 (Box 063A, Folder 4)
- Loose Papers (Box 063A, Folder 5)
  John D. Rockefeller property leases from John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (Lakewood, Ormond Beach); accounting issues.
- Estate Work Papers - Cash Reports (Box 063A, Folder 1)
- Estate of John D. Rockefeller - Current Papers, 1938-1942 (Box 063A, Folder 2)
- Estate of John D. Rockefeller - Correspondence and Reports, 1930-1949 (Box 063A, Folder 3)
- Data Relative to the Death of John D. Rockefeller on May 23, 1937 (Box 063A, Folder 4)
- Loose Papers (Box 063A, Folder 5)
- Standard Oil Company (Ohio) - 60th Anniversary - "With Best Wishes to John D. Rockefeller on the 60th Anniversary of the Founding of the Standard Oil Company (Ohio)" (Box 64, Folder 1)
  Presentations to John D. Rockefeller, Sr.